EDMARK TUAZON

Cavite, Philippines · 09707688781 Email: edmark.softdev@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/edmarktuazon/ Website Portfolio: https://edmarktuazon.onrender.com/

GitHub: https://github.com/edmarktuazon/



I' am self-taught, freelance/part-time Frontend Web Developer based in Cavite, Philippines I specialized in Frontend Web Development. I'm focus on creating responsive and user-friendly websites, I use the latest frontend technologies to bring my client visions to project. I'm dedicated to providing good quality solutions that meet the needs and goals of my clients, as a self-taught Frontend Web Developer, I honed my skills through continuous learning and exploring.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT

PROJECT BASED JR. FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, TEAMHOLIX
COMMMUNICATION DESIGN INC

- Build responsive and user-friendly websites for individuals, groups, startups, and small businesses.
- Converting UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
 Technologies (HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS/Bootstrap 4/5, JavaScript and PHP)
- Implementing clean codes, report, and debug operations in the User Interface.
- Identifying and fixing website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and User Interface responsive issues.
- Handling (FTP FileZilla Client) for uploading every done project and for User Interface
 Testing
- Editing/adding content such as information and layout of past website that they created
- Collaborate with fellow Web Developer using GitHub

JULY 2021 – DECEMBER 2022

FREELANCE FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, FIVERR AND OUTSIDE FIVERR

- Worked with various clients from local and outside the country, providing quality solutions for their businesses or clients
- Developed UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
 Technologies (HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript)
- Worked with existing website of my clients and supporting client's needs after a project
- Provide academic assisting and developing school projects of my student clients such as
 Web Development and Web Designing

DECEMBER 2020 – JANUARY 2021

FREELANCE LANDING PAGE DEVELOPER, PREVIOUS EMPLOYER: DANICA MADELA AND SHAWN JOSIAH

- One month contract and hired me as a landing page developer
- Developed 30 pages of contact form landing page with different designs, for their business campaign

EDUCATION

TERTIARY

JUNE 2020 - JULY 2023

COMPUTER SCIENCE, IMUS COMPUTER COLLEGE, CAVITE

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

JULY 2018 - APRIL 2020

SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY ENGINEERING AND MATHEMATICS (STEM STRAND), SAINT JUDE PARISH SCHOOL CAVITE

INTERNSHIP

SEPTEMBER 25, 2021 – FEBRUARY 22, 2022

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, LINKHELPERS INTERNATIOANAL INC.

- Completed 300 hours of On-The-Job Training remotely
- Designed mockup using Figma and converted into responsive Web Page using (HTML5, CSS (SASS), and JavaScript)
- Implemented formspree (Alternative database) a custom form with no server code
- Worked in SEO list directories
- Conducted daily report about the progress of my task

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND QUALIFICATION

- Programming (Fundamental Java, C++ and VB)

 Source Control Management (Git, GitHub)
- Web (HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Tailwind CSS,
 Adobe Creative Suite (Adobe XD, Figma) Bootstrap 4/5, JavaScript, VueJS, Fundamental ¡Query, TypeScript and PHP)

CERTIFICATES

• Certificate of Completion - On-the-job training

LinkHelpers International Inc.

S.Y 2022 - 2023

• 1st Runner Up - Web Development Competition

Imus Computer College, Cavite

November 2022

Certificate of Participation - Introduction to Electronic Commerce using Shopify

Imus Computer College, Cavite

November 2022

REFERENCES

References are available upon request